Roshan Kumar

Gurugram, Haryana



linkedin.com/in/roshankrsoni



roshankrsoni1@gmail.com



www.roshankrsoni.in



+918340662031

Summary

A Goal-oriented Full-stack developer having more than 2 years & 10 months of experience with a great passion in both back-end and front-end development,I can create API and decent UI.

Armed with a deep sense of responsibility and possessing very high levels of enthusiasm to give my 110% for any endeavor.

I would like to be a part of an organization where I could use and enhance my knowledge and talent for the development of both the organization and myself.

Experience

Software development Engineer

Asort Dec 2019 - Present

Working on fashion e-commerce and lifestyle projects built in React/Redux, NodeJs, Javascript, PostgreSQL, RestAPI etc.

Full-stack Developer

Jai Infoway Oct 2018 - Dec 2019

Built the extensive project from scratch to the end. Has everything that a complex web-app needs. Built-in Angular, Nodejs, Javascript, PostgreSQL, Git, GCP etc.

Web Developer

Sankrit Infotech Jul 2017 - Sep 2018

Web Solutions, ERP Consultancy, Human Resource Recruitment, SEO services and Corporate Training.
As the Web developer I worked on both
Front-end (HTML5, CSS3, Javascript) + Back-end (PHP, MySql).

Education



Dr. C. V. Raman University, Kota Bilaspur Bachelor of Computer Application - BCA 2014 - 2017

Skills

Web Technologies

React/Redux,
Angular JS,
NodeJS, ExpressJS,
HTML5, CSS3, Javascript

Database

PostgreSQL, MongoDB, Firebase etc.

Web Debug Tools

Chrome developer tools, React/Redux DevTools

Linting

VSCode, ESLint, Prettier setup

Versioning and other tools

Git, GitHub, NPM, Yarn

Deployment Tools

GCP, Now.sh, AWS

Other tools

WebPack, Wordpress, Video editing etc.

Daily Activities and Hobbies

Travelling, Listening to Music, Photography, Netflix, Reading.